A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Assembly and Senate Memos, Series 3 FA354
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Assembly and Senate Memos, Series 3
1959-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
Boyd, Joseph H.
Whitman, Ann
Ronan, William J. (William John)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
Cannon, James M.
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
New York (State). State Commission for Human Rights
Morrow, Hugh
New York (State). Dept. of Civil Service
FA354
46 Box(es)
Biographical/Historical note
Nelson A. Rockefeller served as governor of New York from January 1, 1959, to December 18, 1973. He was the first person elected to four consecutive four-year terms as a state governor.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 15 3
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for scholarly research, except where particular restrictions are noted.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Scope and Contents note
This series contains a comprehensive collection of the bills submitted to Nelson A. Rockefeller for approval during his tenure as Governor of New York, an office he held from 1959 to 1973. As the chief executive of the state, Rockefeller signed all bills into law or vetoed them. Each bill that was submitted to Rockefeller for his signature was accompanied by a memorandum from the Counsel to the Governor. These memoranda stated the subject and purpose of the bill, including the original sponsor of the bill; brief comments offering background on the legislation; and the recommendation of the Counsel. The Counsel would usually conclude the memo with a recommendation of "Approval" or "Disapproval." In either case, the legislation may also have been signed or vetoed with an accompanying memorandum from Rockefeller.
Bills from the Legislature included some that were very specific (e.g., Assembly Bill 3228, submitted to the Governor, April 4, 1962, which extended "from May 1 to May 31 the period during which certain specified officers may kill dogs pursuing or killing deer"). This bill was approved. Others reflect a special interest (e.g., a 1970 bill "to provide certain members of the Nassau County Police Department with a retirement allowance equal to 'full salary at the date of retirement' after 35 years of service"). It was disapproved on the recommendation of the Nassau County government and the Offices of Civil Service and Budget.
The series concludes with two folders of "Memoranda of Law" that address issues arising in New York State that required extra-legislative action, for example, a November 7, 1960, memorandum concerning the "Governor's Action to Impound Election Records." Such memoranda were written to inform the Governor of a question or a challenge regarding a recently enacted law or action by the state government.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Appointments Office (FA353)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Joseph H. Boyd (FA355)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, James Cannon (FA356)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Affirmative Action (N. Lee Cook) (FA357)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Counsel's Office (FA358)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York State Committee to Reelect the President (FA359)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Jerry A. Danzig (FA360)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Executive Chamber (FA361)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, 55th Street (FA362)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Issue Books (FA363)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Arthur Massolo (FA364)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Hugh Morrow (FA242)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Office (FA365)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Civil Service Resolutions (Charles H. Palmer) (FA366)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Political Files (FA367)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Press Office (FA368)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Public Relations (FA369)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Departmental Reports (FA370)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, William J. Ronan (FA371)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Speeches (FA372)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Diane Van Wie (FA373)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Ann C. Whitman, Gubernatorial (FA374)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Gene Wyckoff (FA375)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Republican State Fund Raising Reports (FA376)
Affirmative action programs -- New York (State); Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; Human rights; International economic relations; Civil defense -- United States; Civil defense; Arms control -- United States; Arms control; New York (N.Y.); New York (State); Political campaigns -- United States; Political science; International relations; International relations -- United States; Latin America; Legislation -- New York (State); Public relations; State governments -- United States; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Public policy; United States; Vice-Presidents -- United States; Economics; Federal government -- United States; Civil service; Civil service -- New York (State); Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1962; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Government policy; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1958; Presidential campaigns -- United States; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- )
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 9-684 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 688-1151 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 152-1523 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 1525-1820 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 1826-2125 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 2133-2252 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 2253-2481 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 2502-2654 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 2655-2797 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 2798-2926 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 2929-3076 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 3079-3188 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 3192-3336 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 3367-3551 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 3554-3735 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 3736-3864 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 3866-4046 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 4048-4171 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 4177-4323 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 4325-4409 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 1959 Assembly Internal Memo 4416-4438 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 28-672 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 674-1063 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 1064-1322 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 1327-1858 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 1859-2189 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 2193-2594 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 2596-2993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 3016-3354 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 3355-3651 (Box 3, Folder 0029A)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 3653-3881 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 3882-4155 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 4165-4420 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 4426-4582 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- 1960 Assembly Internal Memo 4583-4727 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 43-894 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 905-1223 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 1226-1594 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 1597-1998 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 2014-2436 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 2443-2759 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 2762-3142 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 3151-3508 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 3509-3731 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 3740-3999 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 4002-4225 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 4241-4456 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 4463-4677 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 4678-4862 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- 1961 Assembly Internal Memo 4870-4992 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 25-1036 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 1038-1485 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 1490-1905 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 1970-2298 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 2312-2647 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 2648-2900 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 2905-3403 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 3415-3699 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 3702-4024 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 4031-4286 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 4294-4562 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 4565-4863 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 4864-5025 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- 1962 Assembly Internal Memo 5026-5196 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 20-247 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 250-871 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 877-1241 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 1242-1772 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 1773-2215 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 2234-2669 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 2679-3228 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 3234-3606 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 3927-4130 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 3610-3926 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 4131-4329 (Box 8, Folder 74)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 4333-4538 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 4540-4758 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 4763-4918 (Box 9, Folder 77)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 4920-5052 (Box 9, Folder 78)
- 1963 Assembly Internal Memo 5053-5189 (Box 9, Folder 79)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 1-581 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 604-1281 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 1291-1708 (Box 9, Folder 82)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 1716-1970 (Box 9, Folder 83)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 1977-2349 (Box 9, Folder 84)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 2358-2847 (Box 10, Folder 85)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 2848-3158 (Box 10, Folder 86)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 3161-3600 (Box 10, Folder 87)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 3611-4030 (Box 10, Folder 88)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 4031-4244 (Box 10, Folder 89)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 4245-4450 (Box 10, Folder 90)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 4435-4659 (Box 10, Folder 91)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 4660-4894 (Box 10, Folder 92)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 4898-5112 (Box 10, Folder 93)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 5125-5260 (Box 11, Folder 94)
- 1964 Assembly Internal Memo 5261-5397 (Box 11, Folder 95)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 9-530 (Box 11, Folder 96)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 531-1116 (Box 11, Folder 97)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 1130-1843 (Box 11, Folder 98)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 1868-2194 (Box 11, Folder 99)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 2195-2440 (Box 11, Folder 100)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 2442-2856 (Box 11, Folder 101)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 2857-3092 (Box 11, Folder 102)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 3101-3275 (Box 12, Folder 103)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 3282-3571 (Box 12, Folder 104)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 3575-3861 (Box 12, Folder 105)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 3862-4061 (Box 12, Folder 106)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 4063-4284 (Box 12, Folder 107)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 4285-4519 (Box 12, Folder 108)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 4534-4759 (Box 12, Folder 109)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 4763-4964 (Box 12, Folder 110)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 4972-5187 (Box 12, Folder 111)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 5190-5434 (Box 13, Folder 112)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 5436-5680 (Box 13, Folder 113)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 5683-5891 (Box 13, Folder 114)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 5900-6080 (Box 13, Folder 115)
- 1965 Assembly Internal Memo 6085-6176 (Box 13, Folder 116)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 5-846 (Box 13, Folder 117)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 847-1472 (Box 13, Folder 118)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 1473-1819 (Box 13, Folder 119)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 1820-2200 (Box 13, Folder 120)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 2236-2632 (Box 14, Folder 121)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 2634-2997 (Box 14, Folder 122)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 3010-3447 (Box 14, Folder 123)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 3451-3921 (Box 14, Folder 124)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 3923-4180 (Box 14, Folder 125)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 4184-4466 (Box 14, Folder 126)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 4471-4901 (Box 14, Folder 127)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 4912-5232 (Box 14, Folder 128)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 5240-5494 (Box 14, Folder 129)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 5513-5769 (Box 15, Folder 130)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 5772-6007 (Box 15, Folder 131)
- 1966 Assembly Internal Memo 6009-6155 (Box 15, Folder 132)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 2-738 (Box 15, Folder 133)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 779-1460 (Box 15, Folder 134)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 1493-1943 (Box 15, Folder 135)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 1953-2250 (Box 15, Folder 136)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 2251-2660 (Box 15, Folder 137)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 2664-2912 (Box 15, Folder 138)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 2935-3421 (Box 15, Folder 139)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 3426-3786 (Box 16, Folder 140)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 3787-4367 (Box 16, Folder 141)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 4378-4734 (Box 16, Folder 142)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 4739-4986 (Box 16, Folder 143)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 4987-5421 (Box 16, Folder 144)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 5429-5808 (Box 16, Folder 145)
- 1967 Assembly Internal Memo 5809-6076 (Box 16, Folder 146)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 2-760-A (Box 16, Folder 147)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 799-1570 (Box 16, Folder 148)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 1572-2236-A (Box 17, Folder 149)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 2266-2825 (Box 17, Folder 150)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 2846-3310 (Box 17, Folder 151)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 3311-3623-A (Box 17, Folder 152)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 3628-A-4089 (Box 17, Folder 153)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 4096-4675 (Box 17, Folder 154)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 4683-5083 (Box 17, Folder 155)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 5085-5458-C (Box 17, Folder 156)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 5471-5684 (Box 17, Folder 157)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 5689-6155 (Box 18, Folder 158)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 6161-6315-A (Box 18, Folder 159)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 6316-6539 (Box 18, Folder 160)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 6545-6771-A (Box 18, Folder 161)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 6774-7084 (Box 18, Folder 162)
- 1968 Assembly Internal Memo 7087-7177 (Box 18, Folder 163)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 29-1032 (Box 18, Folder 164)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 1096-1770-A (Box 18, Folder 165)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 1773-C-2279-A (Box 18, Folder 166)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 2306-2874 (Box 19, Folder 167)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 2878-A-3410-A (Box 19, Folder 168)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 3418-3910 (Box 19, Folder 169)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 3912-4581 (Box 19, Folder 170)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 4593-A-4962-B (Box 19, Folder 171)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 4967-5537 (Box 19, Folder 172)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 5346-A-5750 (Box 19, Folder 173)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 5751-6182 (Box 19, Folder 174)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 6185-A-6597 (Box 19, Folder 175)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 6606-6867 (Box 20, Folder 176)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 6868-7084 (Box 20, Folder 177)
- 1969 Assembly Internal Memo 7097-7210 (Box 20, Folder 178)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 4-B-532-A (Box 20, Folder 179)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 536-1089 (Box 20, Folder 180)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 1099-1658-A (Box 20, Folder 181)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 1659-2234 (Box 20, Folder 182)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 2238-2666 (Box 20, Folder 183)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 2638-3265 (Box 20, Folder 184)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 3274-3967-A (Box 21, Folder 185)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 3968-4709 (Box 21, Folder 186)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 4730-5047-A (Box 21, Folder 187)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 5051-A-5570 (Box 21, Folder 188)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 5581-A-5920 (Box 21, Folder 189)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 5923-6262 (Box 21, Folder 190)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 6282-6488 (Box 21, Folder 191)
- 1970 Assembly Internal Memo 6493-6828 (Box 21, Folder 192)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 1-852-A (Box 21, Folder 193)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 857-1643-A (Box 22, Folder 194)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 1744-2436 (Box 22, Folder 195)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 2438-A-3004 (Box 22, Folder 196)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 3006-3607-A (Box 22, Folder 197)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 3617-4117 (Box 22, Folder 198)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 4126-4676-A (Box 22, Folder 199)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 4687-5230 (Box 22, Folder 200)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 5243-B-5649 (Box 22, Folder 201)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 5651-5948 (Box 22, Folder 202)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 5950-A-6254-A (Box 23, Folder 203)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 6280-6719-A (Box 23, Folder 204)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 6821-6972 (Box 23, Folder 205)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 6974-B-7113-B (Box 23, Folder 206)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 7114-7473 (Box 23, Folder 207)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 7501-7790 (Box 23, Folder 208)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 7792-7996 (Box 23, Folder 209)
- 1971 Assembly Internal Memo 7997-8105 (Box 23, Folder 210)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 19-A-4385 (Box 23, Folder 211)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 4387-7780 (Box 23, Folder 212)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 7817-A-8351-A (Box 24, Folder 213)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 8352-A-8647 (Box 24, Folder 214)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 8651-A-8862 (Box 24, Folder 215)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 8869-9245-A (Box 24, Folder 216)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 9247-9617 (Box 24, Folder 217)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 9630-A-10263-A (Box 24, Folder 218)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 10276-10600-A (Box 24, Folder 219)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 10602-10871-A (Box 24, Folder 220)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 10878-11284-A (Box 24, Folder 221)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 11285-11621 (Box 25, Folder 222)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 11627-11819 (Box 25, Folder 223)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 11822-12060 (Box 25, Folder 224)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 12062-12220 (Box 25, Folder 225)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 12221-12329 (Box 25, Folder 226)
- 1972 Assembly Internal Memo 12230-12407 (Box 25, Folder 227)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 1-352 (Box 25, Folder 228)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 373-785 (Box 25, Folder 229)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 814-B-1192 (Box 25, Folder 230)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 1194-B-1558 (Box 26, Folder 231)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 1561-A-2181 (Box 26, Folder 232)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 2183-2911-B (Box 26, Folder 233)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 2933-3803 (Box 26, Folder 234)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 3817-4136-A (Box 26, Folder 235)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 4146-4645 (Box 26, Folder 236)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 4652-A-5308-B (Box 26, Folder 237)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 5320-5907 (Box 26, Folder 238)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 5950-6401-D (Box 26, Folder 239)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 6404-6690-A (Box 26, Folder 240)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 6695-7259-B (Box 27, Folder 241)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 7260-7456 (Box 27, Folder 242)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 7460-A-7729 (Box 27, Folder 243)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 7733-7972 (Box 27, Folder 244)
- 1973 Assembly Internal Memo 7974-8138 (Box 27, Folder 245)
- Extraordinary Session Assembly and Senate Internal Memos (Box 27, Folder 246)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 22-575 (Box 27, Folder 247)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 579-849 (Box 27, Folder 248)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 864-1141 (Box 27, Folder 249)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 1162-1436 (Box 27, Folder 250)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 1444-1740 (Box 27, Folder 251)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 1741-1969 (Box 28, Folder 252)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 1970-2236 (Box 28, Folder 253)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 2239-2449 (Box 28, Folder 254)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 2450-2643 (Box 28, Folder 255)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 2647-2850 (Box 28, Folder 256)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 2851-3138 (Box 28, Folder 257)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 3143-3315 (Box 28, Folder 258)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 3316-3454 (Box 28, Folder 259)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 3455-3668 (Box 28, Folder 260)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 3678-3747 (Box 28, Folder 261)
- 1959 Senate Internal Memo 3748-3898 (Box 28, Folder 262)
- 1960 Senate Internal Memo 6-731 (Box 29, Folder 263)
- 1960 Senate Internal Memo 734-1124 (Box 29, Folder 264)
- 1960 Senate Internal Memo 1129-1807 (Box 29, Folder 265)
- 1960 Senate Internal Memo 1808-2342 (Box 29, Folder 266)
- 1960 Senate Internal Memo 2347-2713 (Box 29, Folder 267)
- 1960 Senate Internal Memo 2715-3191 (Box 29, Folder 268)
- 1960 Senate Internal Memo 3195-3538 (Box 29, Folder 269)
- 1960 Senate Internal Memo 3542-3789 (Box 29, Folder 270)
- 1960 Senate Internal Memo 3790-3934 (Box 30, Folder 271)
- 1961 Senate Internal Memo 4-734 (Box 30, Folder 272)
- 1961 Senate Internal Memo 740-1155 (Box 30, Folder 273)
- 1961 Senate Internal Memo 1157-1657 (Box 30, Folder 274)
- 1961 Senate Internal Memo 1682-2097 (Box 30, Folder 275)
- 1961 Senate Internal Memo 2098-2493 (Box 30, Folder 276)
- 1961 Senate Internal Memo 2498-2953 (Box 30, Folder 277)
- 1961 Senate Internal Memo 2955-3169 (Box 30, Folder 278)
- 1961 Senate Internal Memo 3171-3546 (Box 31, Folder 279)
- 1961 Senate Internal Memo 3558-3842 (Box 31, Folder 280)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 10-806 (Box 31, Folder 281)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 807-1184 (Box 31, Folder 282)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 1186-1759 (Box 31, Folder 283)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 1760-2144 (Box 31, Folder 284)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 2151-2598 (Box 31, Folder 285)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 2599-2793 (Box 31, Folder 286)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 2794-3140 (Box 31, Folder 287)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 3142-3487 (Box 31, Folder 288)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 3512-3767 (Box 32, Folder 289)
- 1962 Senate Internal Memo 3773-3937 (Box 32, Folder 290)
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 11-669 (Box 32, Folder 291)
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 671-1189 (Box 32, Folder 292)
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 1190-1650 (Box 32, Folder 293)
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 1653-2118 (Box 32, Folder 294)
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 2119-2419 (Box 32, Folder 295)
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 2421-2693 (Box 32, Folder 296)
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 2694-3006 (Box 32, Folder 297)
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 3020-3295 (Box 33, Folder 298)